all_questions = [{"question": "Top 5 largest countries by area",
                  "answers":["Russia", "China", "Canada", "USA", "Brazil"]
                  },
                  {"question": "Name the 5 most spoken languages in the world",
                  "answers":["Mandarin", "Spanish", "English", "Hindi", "Bengali"]
                  },

                  {"question": "Name the 5 largest planets in our solar system",
                  "answers":["Jupiter", "Saturn", "Uranus", "Neptune", "Earth"]
                  },
                  {"question": "Name the 5 richest companies",
                  "answers":["Apple", "Microsoft", "Saudi Aramco", "Alphabet", "Amazon"]
                  },
                  {"question": "Top 5 most-followed celebrities on Instagram",
                  "answers":["Ronaldo", "Messi", "Selena Gomez", "Kylie Jenner", "The Rock"]
                  },
                 {"question": "Top 5 most popular superheroes",
                 "answers": ["Spiderman", "Batman", "Superman", "Ironman", "Wonder Woman"]
                },
                {"question": "Top 5 most iconic musical bands",
                 "answers": ["Beatles", "Queen", "BTS", "Coldplay", "The Rolling Stones"]
                },

                {"question": "Top 5 largest countries by number of schools",
                 "answers": ["India", "China", "USA", "Indonesia", "Brazil"]
                },
                 {"question": "Top 5 largest organs in the human body",
                  "answers": ["Skin", "Liver", "Brain", "Lungs", "Heart"]
                  },
                 {"question": "Top 5 elements most abundant in Earthâ€™s crust",
                  "answers": ["Oxygen", "Silicon", "Aluminium", "Iron", "Calcium"]
                  },
                 {"question": "Top 5 brightest objects in the night sky (after the Sun)",
                  "answers": ["Moon", "Venus", "Jupiter", "Mars", "Sirius"]
                  },
                  {"question": "Top 5 most populated countries",
                  "answers":["India", "China", "USA", "Indonesia", "Pakistan"]
                  },
                  {"question": "Top 5 largest cities (by metro population)",
                  "answers":["Tokyo", "Delhi", "Shanghai", "Sao Paulo", "Mexico City"]
                  },



                 ]